波士顿剑桥大学橄榄球筹款活动
注意
Heads up!
恩佐来了
Uh, hey, Enzo's here.
丹  最近过的咋样  兄弟
Dan. Ha ha! What up, bro?
不错  你呢
Doing good. You?
没什么可抱怨的  生意很好
I can't complain. Business is good.
给我们送纸杯蛋糕吗
You bring me cupcakes?
是啊  我让蛋糕店的人都在工作
Yeah, I got them all working at the bakery.
马库斯怎么样了
How's Marcus?
不太好  要做手术
Not good. Has to have surgery.
和你一样
Same as what happened to you.
该死
Damn.
他在哪儿
Where's he at?
先给我洗车
You can clean my ride.
然后我们谈谈
Then let's talk.
好的
Okay.
天啊
Oh, my god.
报警
Call 911!
快拿毛巾
Somebody get us a towel!
-撑住  伙计  -来按住
- Come on, buddy. - Let's keep pressure on it.
撑住  恩佐  撑住
Come on, Enzo. Come on, buddy.
不  我说真的  我不介意在周日工作
No, seriously, I don't mind working on sundays.
是啊  谋杀犯们周日都休息
Yeah, murderers tend to take a break on the lord's day.
那马特潘三连环杀人案是咋回事
What about that mattapan triple homicide?
这个案子是个例外
Well, expect for that, yeah.
-弗罗斯特  你妈来了  -好啊  妈
- Frost, your mom's here. - Hey, mom.
怎么这么快就到了
How'd you get here so fast?
我们提前走了  路上也没堵车
We got off to an early start, no traffic on the 95.
-你好  -你好  罗宾
- Hey. - Hey, Robin.
你怎么也来了
What are you doing here?
卡梅隆在放假
Oh, Cameron's on vacation.
很无聊  他还从没来过波士顿呢
He was bored, so, never been to Boston.
-你好  小卡  -你好
- Hey, Cam. - Hey.
我们要去坐鸭子船
We're gonna ride the duck boat.
真棒
Cool, man.
你好  卡米尔
Hi, Camille.
-简  最近怎么样  -挺好
- Jane. How are you? - I'm good.
谢谢  好久不见了
Thank you. It's been a long time.
这是罗宾  我妈的室友  这是她儿子卡梅隆
This is Robin, my mom's roommate, and her son, Cameron.
很高兴见到你
So nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你  我是简  你好
Nice to meet you. I'm jane. Hi.
-你好  -这是我弟弟弗兰基
- Hi. - This is my brother frankie.
你好啊
Hey, how you doing?
你们怎么没穿警服呢
How come you don't have a police uniform?
事实上  警探不穿警服
Actually, detectives don't wear uniforms.
但是我今天当班
But I'm just on call today.
我们要去打垒球
We're gonna go play some softball.
等等我们
Wait for us!
你们这是要去打保龄球吗
Are you going bowling?
不是  我们想要打
No. We want to play
波士顿警局垒球联赛
for boston police department's softball league.
注意咯
Heads up! Oop.
真好
Yeah.
准备工作做的不错
Good job breaking it in.
把商标取下来
Take off the tag.
季后赛再见了
Goodbye, playoffs.
不妙
Uh...shoot.
这个赛季要结束了
The season's almost over,
所以或许你们明年再来
So, you know, may-- maybe next year.
-扫兴  -等下  看看我听懂了没
- Bummer. - Hold on. Let me make sure I understand.
你的科学家同事
Your science colleagues,
你应该知道
Who, for all you know,
他们可能是世界级的垒球明星
could be world-class softball stars,
你却不让他们参加你的训练
Aren't welcome at your softball practice?
-不行  -那个
- no. Uh...well...
里佐利
Rizzoli.
艾尔斯医生
Dr. Isles.
好的  我马上就到
Okay. I'll be right there.
这事儿还没完
We're not done here.
好的
Okay.
受害者是恩佐・沃马克
Victim is Enzo Womack.
BCU橄榄球队的跑卫
The running back from BCU?
达阵区蛋糕的甜点师
The dessertier from end zone cakes?
你不会说"甜点师"这仨子字吧
Did you just say "Dessertier"?
恩佐・沃马克可是个有名的蛋糕师
Enzo Womack is a well-known cakemaker.
他刚刚在查尔斯街开了一家DIY
He just opened his first D.I.Y. on charles street.
DIY是啥
D.I.Y.?
自己动手装饰  是我的愿望之一
"Decorate it yourself." It's on my bucket list.
怎么回事
What happened?
脖子被刺了两下
Stabbed twice in the neck.
他应该是来支持BCU的筹款活动的
He was probably here to support the bcu fundraiser.
有目击者吗
Any witnesses?
在洗车过程中被杀  没有人看到
Happened in the car wash. Nobody saw anything.
100多个人在这里晃来晃去
We got a hundred people in and out of here.
这是个岔路  一个目击者都没有吗
It's a huge intersection. We don't have one witness?
车开进去以后就没有别人在场了
Once you drive in, it's just you, your vehicle,
自动化的设备  六分钟搞定
and automated equipment for six minutes.
或许有人藏在车里面
Maybe someone was hiding in the van.
知道车是打哪儿开来的吗
Do we know where he was coming from?
他的蛋糕店  达阵区蛋糕
His bakery, end zone cakes.
他的绰号就是达阵
His nickname was "End zone"
因为他有很多次达阵得分
'cause he made so many touchdowns.
谁把他从车上搬下来的
Who removed his body from the van?
丹・麦肯齐  球队助教
Dan MacKenzie, team trainer.
他和教练想要救他
He and the coach tried to revive him.
麦肯齐和恩佐是朋友
MacKenzie and Enzo were friends.
是  他们一起踢球
Yeah, I think they played together.
是啊  麦肯齐是踢球手
Yeah, MacKenzie was a kicker.
他们一起打了四个赛季
Played together for four seasons.
球队现在很乱
Team's a mess.
犯罪现场也是一样
So is the crime scene.
找到他的手机
Found his cellphone.
我有不好的预感  它应该不会有什么帮助
I got a bad feeling this isn't gonna be much help.
好  把货车移到罪证车库
All right, let's get the van back to the evidence garage.
悠闲的周末结束了
So much for a slow sunday.
如果我在那个笼子里练习挥棒会怎么样
What if I practiced my swing in that cagey thing?
那叫击球网  莫拉
It's called a batting cage, Maura.
我找科萨克警司
I'm looking for sergeant detective Korsak.
他来这儿干什么
What is he doing here?
凯西
Casey.
简
Jane.
你好
Hi.
我不知道你今天会在这里
I didn't know you'd be here today.
我在这儿工作啊
I work here.
你好  莫拉
Hello, Maura.
凯西  你好吗
Casey, how are you?
还行
I'm okay.
我  我等会儿去楼下找你
Uh, I'll -- I'll just meet you downstairs.
好的
Okay. Okay.
抱歉  刚才的打招呼很糟糕
I'm sorry. That wasn't much of a greeting.
我再来一次
Let me start again. Okay.
你好  简
Hello, Jane.
你好  见到你真好
Hello. It's good to see you.
我说过  我准备好的时候会联系你
I said I'd, uh, be in touch when I was ready.
所以我猜你还没准备好
So, I'm guessing you're not ready.
很复杂  但是快了
It's complicated. I'm getting closer, though.
好  那么你来这里做什么
Okay. So -- so, why are you here?
我需要找科萨克警司
I need to talk to, uh, sergeant Korsak.
艾西
Elsie! Hey!
你好小妞  你好  凯西
Hello, girl. Hi, Casey.
你好  文斯
Hey, Vince.
那我走了
All right, well,
不妨碍你和科萨克谈话
You know, I don't want to get between you and korsak.
我只是来问问他能不能帮我照看艾西
Oh, I just stopped by to ask if he would watch Elsie for me.
见到你真好
God, it's good to see you.
你随时都可以见我
You can see me anytime you want.
保持联系
I'll be in touch.
我保证  我会的
I promise -- I will.
你知道我在哪儿
Well, you know where I am.
我就是那个打开盒子的小孩
I'm the kid that open the box
盒子上写着"圣诞节才能打开"
that said "Do not open until christmas."
不  是十一月
No, I mean in november.
妈曾经逮到我钻到床下
Ma caught me crawling under her bed
找我的生日礼物
looking for my birthday presents.
你知道这事儿有多重要吗
Are you getting how major this is?
莫拉  你根本就没在听
Maura, you're not even listening.
你已经说了凯西31分钟了
You have been talking about Casey for 31 minutes.
我在顿悟  这是一个分水岭
I'm having an epiphany here, a watershed moment.
我在人生的转折点
I am having a life-altering experience.
能把那个金属探针递给我吗
Can you hand me the metal probe?
可以
Yes.
凯西这件事给了我一个
I mean, Casey gave me the perfect opportunity
变得焦躁的完美机会
To be my impatient self --
对他施压  要求答案
You know, to pressure him and demand answers,
但是我没有
And -- and I didn't.
我其实是挺耐心的
Me. I was patient.
你难道不惊讶吗
Isn't that amazing?
确实  能把镊子递给我一下吗
Yes. Can you hand me the forceps?
你不能一直都因为打垒球的事生我气啊
Okay, you cannot still be upset about the softball thing.
这次打垒球的事  嗯哼
This "Softball thing." Hmm.
我把尊严都踩在了脚下
I-I put my pride on the line
在我的下属面前恳请加入这次课外活动
And beg to be included in an extracurricular activity in front of my employees.
你干嘛看的那么重啊
Why is it so important to you?
那为什么搭建部门间的桥梁是那么重要呢
Why is it so important to build interdepartmental bridges?
明显你从未参加过垒球联赛
You've clearly never played in a softball league.
你不想让我们玩是因为你很厉害
You just don't want us to play because you're too competitive
而且觉得我们水平很烂
and you don't think we're any good.
我说的对吗
I'm right, aren't I?
没错
Yes.
至少你还算诚实
At least you're honest.
他依然有着很棒的肌肉
He still has remarkable musculature.
他肯定不吃自己的蛋糕
He must not eat his cakes.
没错
Yeah.
恩佐曾经是这些年来第一个有机会成为
Enzo was the first B.C.U player in years
职业运动员的BCU球员
who could have gone pro.
我觉得在前十字韧带撕裂以后
I'm guessing that wasn't an option
他就没这个机会了
Once he tore his anterior cruciate ligament.
伤疤看起来大概有五年之久了
Scar tissue looks to be about five years old.
BCU传球给"达阵"
B.C.U going for the money with a hand-off to end zone.
天哪  他跑的可真快啊
Man, he was fast.
哦  不
Oh, no!
沃马克被狠狠拦截了
Womack is tackled hard.
他爬不起来了
He's not getting up.
各位  这可不妙
Folks, this does not look good.
人生变化之快令人惊叹
It's amazing how fast your life can change.
夺走凯西一切的不过是个简易爆炸装置
All it took for Casey was an I.E.D.
一些弹片  还有战争
and some shrapnel. And a war.
我猜凯西是顺道来看你
My guess is Casey dropped by to see you.
别猜了  你不擅长
Stop guessing. You're bad at it.
他是过来看科萨克的
He came by to see Korsak.
别再给我计时了  我不说凯西了
Oh, stop timing me. I'll stop talking about Casey.
有一些刀柄的印记
There are hilt marks...
这儿  这儿
There and there.
那些印记可能是由小刀造成的
Those are probably from the knife.
也许是一把小的巴克军用刺刀
A small buck knife, maybe?
很多刀都有刀柄
Well, many knives have hilts --
求生刀  猎刀
Survival knives, hunting knives,
削皮刀  战斗用刀  短刀
Skinning knives, commando knives, tanto knives.
你能停下来吗
Can you please stop?
有某种微粒物质黏在伤口上
Some kind of particulate matter adhered to the wound.
肯定是从刀上掉下来的
Well, that must have come off the knife.
还有白色纤维  在那儿
And white fibers -- there.
我会让罪证化验室拿去分析
I'll have the crime lab analyze all this.
受害者的货车在罪证车库里
Okay, the victim's van is in the evidence garage.
我马上回来
I'll be back.
你能考虑下打垒球的事吗
Will you think about the, uh, "Softball thing"?
好的
Yes.
谢了
Thank you.
不好意思  答案还是不行
Sorry, the answer's still no.
我们找到了一堆蛋糕装饰材料
We got a bunch of cake-decorating stuff.
都被喷出来的动脉血和洗车泡沫给覆盖了
It's all covered with arterial blood spray and car-wash suds.
凶手很聪明
Killer was smart.
他把我们能用于控告的任何机会都给毁了
He ruined any chance we had of making a case with forensics.
看起来当时挺刺激的
Doesn't it seem a little spur of the moment,
在洗车过程中把人刺伤
Stabbing someone in a car wash?
是啊
Yeah.
我马上拍下来再检验一下
I'll get it all photographed and tested.
弗罗斯特在哪儿
Where's Frost?
搜查令批了下来
Well, the warrant came through.
他在捣鼓恩佐的电脑
He's working on Enzo's laptop
还一直试着干燥他的手机
and still trying to dry out his cellphone.
好吧  我会让罪证化验室对比检验
Okay, I'll have the crime lab
这里所有的工具和刀具
comparison-test all the tools and knives in here.
莫拉觉得凶器有刀柄
Maura thinks that the murder weapon had a hilt.
这个就有个刀柄
This has a hilt.
我不知道他会来
I didn't know he was coming.
我了解
Yeah, I figured.
他问了你的很多事情
He asked a lot of questions about you.
真的吗
Really?
为什么他把艾西留给你
Why did he leave Elsie?
我要照顾她一段时间
I'm taking care of her for a while.
他知道如果他带它来  我是不会拒绝的
He knew if he brought her by, I couldn't refuse her.
你要照看它吗  照看多久
You're taking care of her? For how long?
或许几个月吧
Maybe a few months.
为什么啊  他要去哪儿  他没细说
Why? Where's he going? He didn't go into details.
你是个警探  你怎么不问啊
You're a detective. Didn't you ask?
我不想多打听
I didn't want to pry!
男的都是这样
Oh, that's so male.
你觉得这是糖霜吗
You think this is frosting?
可能吧  罪证化验室能检验出来
Maybe. Crime lab can test it.
看啊  我们至少找到了够吃几年的
Look, we got at least several years' worth
糖霜和蛋糕屑了
of frosting and cake crumbs.
"放旦"是什么鬼东西
What the hell is "Fun-dant"?
是方旦糖
Fondant.
那东西很黏很甜还不能吃
And it's sticky, sweet, inedible crap
他们把它放到蛋糕上
That they put on cakes.
别把它放在庆祝退休的蛋糕上
Don't put it on retirement cake.
会注意的
Duly noted.
真是条乖狗  艾西
You're a good girl, elsie.
它是最棒的狗
Oh, she's the best.
还是一条肢障服务犬
And you're a service dog.
凯西需要你  你在这儿干嘛呢
Casey needs you, so what are you doing here?
嘿  妈妈
Hey, ma.
这是弗罗斯特警探的妈妈卡米尔
This is detective Frost's mother, Camille.
很高兴见到你  我是安琪拉
Oh. Nice to meet you. I'm angela.
你好  幸会
Hi. Pleasure.
您在这儿等可以吗
You okay waiting here?
没问题
Yes, yes.
多谢你带着我们四处转悠
And thank you so much for taking us around.
小事一桩  回见  妈妈
Sure. See ya, ma.
再见  宝贝儿
Bye, babe.
多好的一个男人啊
What a nice man.
他开车带着我和我的室友还有她的孩子
He drove me and my roommate and her son
在我们等巴里期间在波士顿四处转悠
all over Boston while we were waiting for Barry.
没错  他是个好孩子
Yeah, he's a good kid.
你儿子和我女儿简就像这个一样
And, uh, your son and my daughter, Jane, are like this.
我希望我能住的近一些
I wish I lived closer.
我觉得我从未见过他一样
I feel like I never see him.
你住在维吉尼亚州对吗
You live in, uh, Virginia, right?
诺福克
Norfolk.
我在那里的一所军校教书
I teach at one of the military universities there.
真好啊  你教什么的
Nice. What do you teach?
土木工程
Civil engineering.
现在我们知道弗罗斯特的智商是遗传谁了
Well, now we know where, uh, detective Frost gets his brains.
他爸爸其实也很聪明
His father was actually pretty smart, too.
我们20年前离了婚
Uh, we divorced 20 years ago.
我刚离婚
I just got divorced.
真对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我不觉得
I'm not.
不再觉得
Well, anymore.
要我帮你拿杯咖啡吗
Can I get you a cup of coffee?
不需要  谢谢
Oh, no, thank you.
我觉得在路上已经喝得够多了
I think I already had enough on the way here.
我一直都在试着鼓起勇气
I'm actually trying to work up the nerve
告诉巴里我准备再婚了
to tell Barry that I'm getting remarried.
恭喜啊
Oh. Congratulations.
为什么这还会让你紧张呢
Why is that making you nervous?
离婚让他很难过
The divorce was hard on him.
并且我从未出去约会过
And I never dated.
别误解我
Well, don't get me wrong.
巴里很尊重我
Barry is very respectful,
但你知道的  他有着很强烈的意见
But knowing him, you know, he has strong opinions.
我们把他们带大
Well, we did bring them up
就是为了让他们有自己的想法
to have their own minds.
没错
Yes, we did.
转变就是如此无常  不是吗
It's crazy how the tables turn, isn't it?
我和这个男的交往有一段时间了
I was seeing this guy for a while,
我的孩子都快疯了
And, uh, my kids went nuts.
那你又怎样了
What'd you do?
感觉很内疚
Felt guilty.
但然后我决定我不能活在别人的世界里
But then I decided I was allowed to be a person, too.
没错
Yes, you are.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
我觉得你应该抱怨一下你的午饭啊
I think you need to complain about your lunch order.
都有个手机掉里头了
There's a phone in it.
大米是种有效的干燥剂
Rice is an effective desiccant.
你用三音节词
Are you using three-syllable words
是因为你妈妈过来了吗
because your mother's in town?
天啊  可能吧
Oh, man. I might be.
能开机吗
Can you make it work?
我不确定  线路很湿滑
I'm not sure. Circuits are wet.
不过我一直在玩恩佐的手提电脑
But I've been having fun on Enzo's laptop.
他喜欢三件事
He liked three things.
让我猜猜  女人  蛋糕和BCU橄榄球队
Let me guess -- women, cakes, and bcu football.
这什么日子  橄榄球  女人和蛋糕
What a life -- football, women, and cake.
恩佐有整季的套票
Enzo was a season-ticket holder.
他硬盘里有波士顿剑桥大学队
And he also had every BUC game
过去十年的比赛录像
from the last 10 years on his hard drive.
真是个认真的粉丝
That's a serious fan.
男人们真是执着
Dude was hardcore.
他每场比赛必看  重播也不错过
He watched every game and a lot of replays.
无疑在电脑上看橄榄球要不了他的命
Pretty sure viewing football on his computer didn't kill him.
是的  我记得他是妇女之友
Yeah, and I remember him to be quite the ladies' man.
他生活中的女人们呢
What about the women in his life?
好多甜点
Ho-ho-ho! Nice assortment of desserts.
我是说纸杯蛋糕
I meant the cupcakes.
是嘛  你确实这么说了
Yeah, sure you did.
她们中大多数是他的前女友
Most of them are his old girlfriends.
他雇了他的旧情人吗
He hired his old flames?
你要什么口味  科萨克
Which flavor would you choose, Korsak?
巧克力  香草
Chocolate? Vanilla?
纸杯蛋糕太多  时间太少
So many cupcakes, so little time.
好吧  我要提出骚扰索赔
Okay, I'm about to file a harassment claim.
骚扰必须是冒犯性的才可以
It has to be hostile and offensive.
继续说
Keep talking.
恩佐在私人日历上更新了他的日程
Enzo updated his schedule on this internal calendar.
他写了他要去洗车募捐
Well, he posted he was going to the car-wash fundraiser.
上午8点  伯明翰城市大学洗车
谁有权限看这个日历
Who had access to that calendar?
只有他的雇员
Just his employees.
你是说只有他的前女友们
You mean just his ex-girlfriends?
看这个
Check this out.
我想这样对待我的前男友
"What I'd like to do to my ex-boyfriend."
你在哪里找到这张照片的
Where'd you find that photo?
她发在猎影时克上了
She posted it on CandidGram.
她整天都在发自拍照
She posted selfies all day long.
劳拉・史蒂芬斯是谁
Okay, who's Laura Stephens?
看上去是个雇员  我查查
She looks like an employee. I'll check.
她24岁
She's 24.
她是达阵区蛋糕店的蛋糕装裱师
She's a cake decorator at end zone cakes.
好吧  走吧
All right, well, come on.
莫拉生我的气了
Maura's mad at me,
我来让她小开心一下
So let's give her a cheap thrill,
她可以去对蛋糕刀做比对
and she can comparison-test the cake knives.
电梯见
Meet me at the elevator.
怎么了
What's up?
你知道我带弗罗斯特他妈
You know how I drove Frost's mom
和她室友闲逛吗
and her roommate around?
知道
Yeah.
我觉得她们是
Well, I think they're, uh...
你懂的
You know.
不  我不懂
No,don't know.
我觉得她们是一对
I think they're a couple.
什么
What?!
弗罗斯特知道吗
Does Frost know?
别在意  不用回答
Never mind. Don't answer that.
这  这和咱们无关
It -- it's none of our business.
他怎么可能知道
No way he knows.
她结婚了  和他爸
She was married -- to his father.
你怎么就认为她们是一对
Well, what makes you think they're a couple?
简  她们是一对
Jane, they're a couple.
不关咱们的事
It's non of our business.
什么不关你的事
What's none of your business?
我们  在谈论我妈
We were...just talking about ma.
听起来像是在谈论她的情感生活
It sounded like you were talking about her love life.
不是  是更年期
No. Menopause.
我们在谈论更年期
We were talking about menopause.
是  是的  你说的对
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
我妈更年期了和我们无关
It's none of our business if ma's in menopause.
回见
See ya.
准备好了吗
You ready?
是的
Yes.
我们要  带上莫拉一起走
We should... get Maura and go.
波士顿凶案组
Boston homicide.
你对恩佐做了什么
What are you doing about Enzo?
你叫什么
What's your name?
瓦伦蒂娜・史密斯
Valentina Smith.
你们怎么能让这事发生呢
How could you let this happen?
洗车本来应该很安全的
Car washes are supposed to be safe!
你和他什么关系
Uh, what was your relationship to him?
我们是大学同学
We went to college together.
我是他的办公室主任
I'm his office manager.
你们谈过恋爱吗
Were you two involved?
大学有过
In college.
我们好几年都没有睡过了
We haven't slept together in years.
你今天早上在哪里
And where were you this morning?
送结婚蛋糕去了
Delivering a wedding cake.
我们要去证实
We'll need to verify that.
随便你们
Whatever.
我不会谋杀老板的
I'm not about to kill my boss.
我们要找劳拉・史蒂芬斯谈谈
We'd like to talk to Laura Stephens.
这里所有人都是他朋友
Everybody here was his friend.
我们现在在为他的追悼会做蛋糕
We're working on a cake for his memorial service now.
他们在做一个波士顿剑桥大学
They're making the Boston Cambridge University
橄榄球场
Football stadium.
看  这是小恩佐
Oh, look! It's a little Enzo.
这个是想表现天堂
And this is a representation of heaven.
我觉得这是一个可以让
And I think that golden ladder
-他爬上去的金梯子  -艾尔斯医生
- is so he can ascend. Uh, Dr. Isles?
比对测试呢
The comparison test?
对哦  当然
Oh, yes, of course.
恩佐爱她们的全部  身材  体型  发色
Damn, Enzo liked them in all shapes, sizes, and colors.
这算骚扰吗
Is that harassment?
也许  算吧
Possibly, yes.
如果你们再靠近一点就打扰到我工作了
You'll interfere with my process if you come any closer.
我们想和你谈谈恩佐・沃马克
We'd like to talk to you about Enzo Womack.
稍等一下好吗
Can you just wait a sec?
我去  你让我撞到了枕颏带
Crap, you made me bump the chin strap.
这些是你的刀吗
Are these your knives?
别碰它们
Don't touch them.
我需要这些刀的粘土印痕来作比对
I'll need a clay impression for a comparison test.
我没杀他  好吗
I didn't kill him, all right?
但一定是某个女人杀了那混蛋
A woman definitely killed that bastard, though.
你怎么知道是女人杀了他
How do you know a woman killed him?
你觉得你能睡了一个姑娘
You think you can sleep with a girl,
给她买早午餐  在她耳边说甜蜜的鬼话
buy her brunch, whisper sweet bullshit in her ear,
然后却说"我们做朋友吧"
and then say, "Let's be friends, 'kay?"
你觉得你能一次又一次这么做吗
You think you can do that over and over?
我们找到了你发的这张照片  劳拉
We found this photo you posted, Laura.
只是个玩笑
It was a joke.
对我来说可没那么可笑
It doesn't seem that funny to me.
我也觉得
Me neither.
看上去很尖锐
That looks pretty sharp.
这是一个花针
It's a flower pin.
去问问别人
You should talk to everybody.
恩佐自始至终都在缠着我们
Enzo strung us all along.
我们做朋友吧  好吗
"Let's be friends, 'kay?"
-不  不好  -那你为什么还为他工作
- No, not okay. - So, why'd you work for him?
你知道在当下的经济状况
Do you know how hard it is
找到一份像样的工作有多难吗
to find a decent job in this economy?
我主修过性别研究
I have a major in gender studies.
我懂你的意思
Ooh. Yeah, I know what you mean.
在我看来
Well, it seems to me that
恩佐的行为促使你杀了他  劳拉
Enzo gave you a reason to kill him, Laura.
他确实该杀  不过我没有
He did, but I didn't.
我当时在健身房  你们可以查
I was at the gym. You can check.
刷卡的时候他们拍了照片
They take a picture when they swipe it.
我要了回来
I want it back.
我晚上还要去健身
I have to work out later today.
真想不到劳拉有这么确凿的不在场证明
It's a shame that Laura has a solid alibi.
我仍然认为恩佐在玩一个危险的游戏
Still, I think Enzo was playing a dangerous game.
你觉得是他的滥交
You think, uh, too many notches
害死了他吗
on the bedpost got him killed?
说不准
Maybe.
莫拉检测完了所有刀
Okay, Maura's finished testing all the knives.
我们的凶器不属于那家蛋糕店
Our murder weapon is not that bakery.
罗宾能陪你妈来真是太好了
So, it's nice that Robin came with your mom,
这样她就有人陪了
You know, so she could have some company.
我妈真的很独立  不过  我猜的
My mom's really independent, but, yeah, I guess.
她们怎么认识的
How do they know each other?
她们都是诺福克海军大学的教授
They're both professors at the naval university in Norfolk.
我不知道你妈是教授
I didn't know your mom was a professor.
我妈的课是海军大学第一批
My mom was in one of the first classes
允许有女老师教讲的课之一
at the naval academy that allowed women.
没开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me?
她可牛了
She's amazing.
她和我爸都上的海军学校
She and my dad were midshipmen together.
他们在那儿认识的
That's how they met.
她在事业上不输我爸
He had the career she should have.
你妈妈和罗宾是室友  对吧
And they're roommates, y-your mom and Robin?
罗宾离婚后  她们决定一起分担开销
After Robin's divorce, they decided to share expenses.
教授赚钱不容易啊
Professors don't make that much.
两人在一起挺好的
Well, it's good they have each other.
我是说  一起分担开销挺好的
I mean to -- to share expenses.
那倒是真的
No kidding.
走吧  下班啦
Come on. Let's call it a day.
这赛季只剩两场比赛了
We got two games left in the season,
今天再不练习的话
and if we don't get in a practice today,
要被缉毒组横扫了
the Drug Unit's gonna kick our ass.
既然你都这么说了
Since you put it that way...
我带上我妈行吗
You think it's okay if -- if I bring my mom?
还有罗宾和卡梅隆
Oh, and -- and Robin and Cameron, too?
当然
Sure.
可以
Yeah.
莫拉
Maura.
简
Jane.
没想到你们连练习都不叫上我们
Can't believe you weren't gonna tell us about practice.
行了  听着  这赛季只剩两场比赛了
Okay...look, there are only two more games left in the season,
再说我们会被取消资格的
and -- and we'll be disqualified.
你们又不是凶案组的
You're not part of homicide.
那弗罗斯特的妈妈就是了吗
Oh, so Frost's mom is part of homicide?
简  我们来猜拳分组  打场练习赛吧
Jane, we could buck up sides and have a scrimmage.
猜拳  你是还没长大吗
Buck up? Who are you, Opie?
-谁还没长大  -别多嘴  亲爱的
- Who's Opie? - Shh. Honey.
莫拉  你们人数不够组成一队
Maura, you -- you don't have enough players for a team.
我们愿意加入莫拉的队伍
Oh, we'd be happy to play for Maura's team.
对啊  好呀
Yeah. Why not?
我俩不过是找个机会锻炼锻炼的老女人
We're just a couple of old ladies looking for some exercise.
好吧
All right.
好了  你要加油了  简
All right. So, you're gonna have to buck up, Jane.
乐意至极
I'd love to.
赢家给输家买喝的  再公平不过了
It's only fair that the winners buy the losers drinks.
科萨克能带卡梅隆去吃冰淇淋
Korsak got to take Cameron to icecream.
我们就得在这儿忍受这个
We got to endure this?
实验室出结果了  艾尔斯医生
Lab results, dr. Isles.
谢谢
Thank you.
货车里可辨认的有机物
All the identifiable organic substances
均为葡萄糖基糖类化合物
in the van were glucose-based confectioner's compounds.
了不起
Swell.
以及血液和肥皂中的甘油
And blood and glycerin from the soap.
超级了不起
Double swell.
除去一种物质
There was one exception.
你们在后车厢垫子上发现的蓝色物质
The blue substance that you found on the rear floor mat
是部分场地油漆
is bulk of field paint.
场地油漆
Field paint?
波士顿剑桥大学的球场是蓝色的
BCU's colors are blue and...
苏西  你能查查那油漆
Susie, can you check and see if
是否来自波士顿剑桥大学吗
that field paint is from BCU?
-是  没问题  -多谢了
- Yeah, sure. - Thank you.
就俩需要锻炼的老太太
Oh, just two old ladies in need of some exercise.
我看有人没说实话
Mm. I think somebody lied.
是实话  我们不就是老太太吗
It wasn't a lie. We are old ladies.
再说我们确实需要锻炼了
And we needed exercise.
比赛太刺激了
It was such an exciting game.
6比1  我们完胜
6-1. We trounced you.
我们
"We"?
卡米尔打出两记本垒打
Camille hit two home runs,
罗宾打出一记满垒本垒打
and Robin hit a grand slam.
所以你得两分  你得四分  你没得分
So 2 for you, 4 for you, and zero for you.
完全正确
Exactly.
这俩枪手替你打了  有你什么事儿
And is it a "we" when you got two ringers?
我的天啊  你早就知道了
Oh, my god! You knew.
我没想到罗宾挥棒还那么有力
Well, I figured Robin's swing had lost some power.
弗罗斯特
Frost!
再说老妈  你都很久没打了
And mom -- you haven't played in a while.
我们也以为自己腿脚不灵活了呢
We thought we were rustier than we were.
我们只得了一分  就一分
We scored one run -- one.
我觉得你们打得挺好的
I think you played really well.
肯定得被缉毒组灭了
The Drug Unit's gonna destroy us.
让我们加入就不会了
Well, not if you let us play.
你说的"我们"是指卡米尔和罗宾吧
And by "us", you mean Camille and Robin?
你真是输不起
You're a very sore loser.
再怎么说我也到第一垒了
I did make it to the first base.
-哪有人说"第" 啊  -什么
- You don't say "the". - What?
你到达了一垒  可你是被保送上垒的
You made it to first base because you were walked.
保送上垒很好啊
You know, walking's good.
-敬保送上垒  -敬保送上垒
- To the walk. - To the walk.
继续保送
Walking.
你踢我腿干嘛
Why are you kicking my leg?
我只能对罗宾和卡米尔拱手示弱了
I s-should hand it to Robin and Camille.
阿刚暗示弗兰基  罗宾和卡米尔手上戴了结婚戒指
简  你伤到脖子了吗  肌肉抽筋了吗
Jane, did you hurt your neck? Are you having a muscle spasm?
还不懂啊
Really?
我要举杯敬酒
I'd like to propose a toast.
这才叫有球品呢
That's great sportsmanship.
看见没  为优胜队举杯庆贺
See? Toasting the winning team.
敬两位好人
Uh, to two wonderful people
她们教会了我爱和承诺的意义
who have taught me the meaning of love and commitment --
我妈妈  还有她的伴侣罗宾
My mom...and her partner, Robin.
巴里  你已经知道了
Barry, you knew?
是的  妈妈  我早知道了
Yeah, mom, I knew.
我都苦恼好几年了
I had been agonizing over this for years.
你从没提过  我也不想多问
You never brought it up. It wasn't my business.
亲爱的
Honey.
我想你愿意说的时候  会告诉我的
I figured if you wanted to tell me, you would.
我就说吧
I told you.
你就是对他没信心
You've never given him enough credit.
为什么不早告诉我呢
I just wish I'd known.
我邀请你们来麻省都多少次啦
How many times have I invited you to Massachusetts?
我一直希望你能让她敞开心扉
I kept hoping you'd make an honest woman out of her.
很高兴你做到了
I'm glad you finally have.
谢谢
Thank you.
恭喜
Congratulations.
是啊  恭喜
Yes, congratulations.
婚礼什么时候办
When is the wedding day?
其实我们还没定日子呢
We actually haven't even set the date yet.
是时候告诉你了  巴里
It's -- it was just time to tell you, Barry.
我结婚不能没有你
I couldn't get married without you.
做我的伴郎怎么样
You'll be our best man?
那是一定的
You know I will.
我正好有件漂亮衣服没穿过呢
Oh, and I have a great dress I haven't worn yet.
人家又没邀请你
You haven't been invited.
听着  我们婚礼那天
Listen, when we have our wedding,
欢迎大家都来
you'll all be welcome.
你们来我们会很高兴的
We'd love to have you join us.
好了  这得上香槟才行
All right, well, this calls for champagne.
输家买单
Losing team is buying.
同意  同意
Hear, hear!
前提是赢的人别再唧唧歪歪了
As long as winning team stops mocking.
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry, sorry!
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
跟你道歉
I wanted to apologize.
道什么歉
Oh? What did you do?
进来吧
Come inside.
不行
I can't.
抱歉  我们就在这儿谈吧
I'm so sorry. We -- we can talk out here.
我不是说我不能爬楼梯
I don't mean I can't make it up your stairs.
我只是不想进去
I mean I don't want to go inside.
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
上楼听你道歉
Upstairs to hear your apology.
那你得等我一会儿
It might take me a while.
行  我反正得把手套收起来
Good. I have to put my glove away.
不行  好吧
No. Okay.
淡定  淡定  淡定
Okay, okay, okay. Okay, okay, okay.
来了
Um, coming!
Coming.
来了  算了
Coming. Okay.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
对  没事
Yeah. I'm fine.
进来吧  请坐
Uh, come in. Um, sit down.
给你拿瓶啤酒  还是
Can -- can I get you a beer or...
拿杯水吧
Maybe a water.
喝水  好的
A water. Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
还记得我上次来的时候
I remember the last time I was here.
就在你最后一次去阿富汗前夜
Right before your last tour in Afghanistan.
我的终极之旅
My final tour.
就像是滑雪道上的最后一滑
It's like the last run on a ski slope.
摔倒的时候才想着早知道不冒这个险了
You know as you're falling you shouldn't have taken it.
谢谢你能上来  我知道你并不想这样
Thank you for coming up. I-I know you didn't want to.
我想  只是
I did. I ju--
我不想离你这么近
I didn't want to be this close to you.
凯西
Casey.
别这样
Please.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我让科萨克警司
I asked Sergeant Korsak
照顾艾西是因为我要动手术
to look after Elsie because I'm having surgery.
手术  什么时候
Surgery? W-when?
快了
Soon.
是干细胞试验
The stem-cell trials?
不  我没有参与试验
No. I'm not a candidate.
我找到一位神经外科医生
I found a neurosurgeon.
他觉得他能取出
He thinks he can remove the, uh, shrapnel
压迫着我脊髓的弹片和骨头碎片
and bone shards from pressing against my spinal cord.
凯西  真是太好了
Casey, that's incredible.
手术是有风险的
There are no guarantees,
而且术后复健还要花很长时间
and, uh...and there will be months of rehab.
但这是我长久以来
But it's the first crack
第一次看到希望
of light I've seen in a pretty dark tunnel.
让我  让我帮你吧
Well, let me -- let me help you.
我想陪着你一起做这些事
I-I want to go through this with you.
我就是不想这样才没有联系你
That's exactly why I didn't get in touch.
凯西  这不要紧的  明白吗
Casey... i-it doesn't matter, okay?
我很在乎你
I care about you.
不
No.
一段关系不该这样开始
This is no way to start a relationship,
而我俩现在就处于这样的开端
and this is where we are -- at the beginning.
好  那我们就快进一下
Okay, well, let's get to the middle.
我想这么做
I want to do this.
照顾一个病人会给亲密关系带来很多丑陋
Taking care of an invalid is an ugly form of intimacy.
这事一点也不浪漫  简
There's no romance in it, Jane.
这种病只是改变了你的外在
This injury isn't you.
你的内心并没有变
This is you.
我应该要你留下的
I should have asked you not to go.
我应该要你等我的
I should have asked you to wait.
我不在的时候你有跟别人约会吗
Did you see someone else while I was gone?
有
Yes.
你在乎过他吗
Did you care about him?
是的
Yes.
那你以后也能找到另一个人
Then you'll find someone again.
什么  不
What? No.
凯西  等一下  等等
Casey, wait a minute. Wait.
我跟那人没什么了  早就结束了
It's over with him. It's -- it's been over.
听着  当我再见到你时我才知道
Look, I realized that when I saw you again
自己有多希望和你在一起
how much I want this to work.
但是不行
This won't work.
可以的
It will.
凯西  就给我一个机会  求你了
Casey, please, just give me a chance. Please.
为我做一件事
Do one thing for me.
做什么都行
Anything.
让我吻你
Let me kiss you...
然后忘了我
and then let me go.
凯西  别这样  求你了
Casey, please, please.
再见了  简
Goodbye, Jane.
袜子都去哪儿了
Where do socks go?
你只需要一个半英寸的空档
All you need is a half-inch gap
让它们从搅拌叶片下面掉出来
for them to slip under the agitator paddle.
所以不是到袜子天堂去了
So not sock heaven.
去你抽屉里找找
Check your drawers.
因为静电它们总跟其他衣物粘在一起
Static electricity causes them to stick to other clothing.
我希望恩佐能去橄榄球天堂
I hope Enzo gets to go to football heaven.
谢谢你过来
Thank you for coming.
别扔了呀
Don't throw them away!
找不到另一只了  形单影只只会让我伤感
They don't have partners. They're making me sad.
好吧  告诉我他说了什么
Okay. Tell me what he said.
他要做手术取出弹片和骨头碎片
He is having surgery to remove bone and shrapnel.
怎么  你表情干嘛那么奇怪
What? What's with the weird look?
没什么
It's nothing.
起疹了  莫拉
Hives, Maura.
即使是善意的谎言也会让你发痒
Even white lies make you itch.
好吧
Okay.
凯西的病被称作马尾神经综合征
Casey's condition is called cauda equina syndrome.
从我在他身上观察到的情况来看
From what I've observed in him,
可能影响了第11和12胸椎  或许还有第1腰椎
it probably involves T-11 and -12 and maybe L-1.
还是那问题  为什么你表情怪怪的
Same question -- why the weird look?
给部分身体受损的截瘫病人动手术非常危险
Surgery on a partially impaired paraplegic is very risky.
你又不是神经外科医生
Well, you're not a neurosurgeon.
你说的对  我不是
You're right. I'm not.
那就别乱猜
So no guessing.
我只想装作一切都会没事的
I just want to pretend like it's all gonna be fine.
你也能这样吗
Can you do that with me?
我可以试试
I can try.
敬礼  艾西  好姑娘
Salute, Elsie. Good girl!
敬得不错  艾西
Good salute, Elsie.
那不是在敬礼
That wasn't a salute.
当然是啦
Yes, it was.
我看更像是握手
Looked like "shake" to me.
谁想要面包圈吗
Anybody want a bagel?
我要  谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
好了  我们进展到哪里了
All right, so, where are we?
什么进展都没有
We are nowhere.
我们最好赶快有所发现
We better get somewhere
不然卡瓦诺夫就要发飙了
or Cavanaugh's gonna tear off some heads.
也许我能帮上忙
Maybe I can help.
都是因为团队建设的垒球赛
Thanks to the team-building softball game,
罪证化验室的人工作了整晚
the crime lab stayed up all night
把这些结果给你弄出来了
to get these results to you.
我还以为他们卖力帮忙破案是因为
I thought they were helping us solve murders because --
那什么  这是他们的本职工作呀
oh, I don't know -- it's their job.
地毯上的蓝色颜料跟波士顿剑桥大学用在
The blue paint on the floor mat is consistent
场地上的颜料是一样的
with the paint used for the BCU field stencils.
那正是凶手曾去过的地方
That's right where the killer would have been.
弗罗斯特  你说恩佐有赛季套票
Frost, you said that Enzo had season tickets.
周六的比赛他去了吗
Was he at Saturday's game?
不  他的票没用过
No. His ticket wasn't used,
所以我联系了他办公室的负责人跟进
so I followed up with his office manager.
恩佐要做一个结婚蛋糕所以没去
Enzo had to work on a wedding cake.
那是赛季的第一场比赛
It was the first game of the season,
也就是说不是恩佐把场地颜料
which means Enzo didn't transfer that field paint
带到他车里的
inside his van.
也许是凶手带去的
Maybe our murderer did.
我原先看的时候还没觉得特别  看看这个
It didn't mean anything when I looked at it, but watch this.
恩佐在看这段周六比赛的录像
Enzo was watching this clip from Saturday's game.
那是什么战术呀
What kind of call is that?
菲利普斯教练  我们对他有什么了解
Coach Phillips? What do we know about him?
简  他的动机会是什么呢
Jane, what would be the motive?
恩佐已经五年没在他手下打球了
Enzo hadn't played for him for five years.
菲利普斯想要争夺一个甲级联盟的教练职位
Phillips was a contender for a division I coaching gig.
五年前波士顿剑桥大学输了那个赛季
It went away after BCU lost that season
这工作也就没戏了
five years ago.
蒂姆・菲利普斯采访
我失望吗  当然  我当然失望
Am I disappointed? Yeah, yeah, I'm disappointed.
成为甲级联盟的教练是我的梦想
Coaching a division I team is a dream of mine.
可是  波士顿剑桥大学
But, uh, BCU --
我们本来胜算在握
we had a great run there
直到恩佐受伤了
till Enzo hurt himself.
听上去菲利普斯是在责怪恩佐
Sounds like Phillips blames Enzo.
蓝色颜料只告诉了我们
Well, that blue paint only tells us
凶手曾经出现在球场上
that our killer was on that field.
弗罗斯特  手机能正常使用了吗
Frost, you get the phone working yet?
还没  得把电池放进去
No. Got to put the battery back in.
好  我想看看恩佐被杀前一晚
Okay, I want to see what else Enzo was watching
还看了些什么
the night before he was killed.
他的电脑在波士顿地区情报中心
His laptop is in BRIC.
好的
Okay.
科萨克警司
Sergeant Korsak,
凯西有没有告诉你为什么要你照顾艾西
did Casey tell you why he needed you to take Elsie?
没有  他只说她可能这几个月需要另一个家
No. He just said she might need a home for a few months.
他跟我说了些事  但我不想让简知道
He mentioned something I didn't want Jane to hear.
说了什么
What was that?
他要我保证如果他发生什么意外
He made me promise I would take care of Elsie
我会照顾艾西
if anything happened to him.
-喂  你们还来不来  -来了
- Hey, you guys coming? - Yep.
好  我们只有一次机会
Okay. We got one shot at this.
只要还有一点水分
If there's any moisture,
电路就会烧坏
the circuits will fry themselves.
开机吧
Turn it on.
有人给我作证吗
Do I have witnesses?
警司科萨克警探
Sergeant detective Korsak
让我开启手机电源
is telling me to turn this phone on.
别废话了赶紧开机  弗罗斯特
Turn the damn phone on, Frost.
我要记录里
I want it in writing
清楚地写明如果手机怎么了不是我的责任
that this one is not on me if this phone...
没戏了
It's dead.
你那大米干燥的主意还是没成功
So much for your rice idea.
这是恩佐看过的所有视频清单
This is the whole list of video files Enzo was watching.
能播一下那个吗
Can you play that one?
波士顿剑桥大学队把球传给"达阵"
BCU going for the money with a hand-off to End Zone.
看啊  沃马克冲入强侧  不
Wow! Look at Womack as he breaks to the strong side and -- oh, no!
他起不来了  看上去不妙啊
He's not getting up. Folks, this does not look good.
恩佐看这个干什么
Ugh. Why was Enzo watching that?
你注意到右后卫了吗
You see the right guard?
-是的  -是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我没有  你们说什么呢
I didn't. What are you talking about?
再看一遍
Let's see that again.
恩佐・沃马克受伤
一向很稳健的右后卫
The normally sure-footed right guard
仿佛滑了一下
looks like he slips on the turf.
然后马丁就冲过来了
And there goes hard-charging Der'on Martin
全速撞击
Flying in at full speed.
恩佐倒下了
Enzo is down! Ouch!
弗罗斯特  放一下周六的比赛片段
Frost, play that clip from Saturday's game.
马库斯接传球跑向右侧
Marcus to the right on a hand-off.
这是怎么回事
Oh! How did that happen?
看上去BCU的右后卫滑倒了
Looks like BCU's right guard lost his footing
于是正向后面跑的姐夫・马库斯
and left running back Jeff Marcus
就毫无防备地遭到重击
unprotected for that nasty hit.
这让我想起五年前
Ouch! It reminds me of that hit
断送了恩佐・沃马克职业生涯的那次撞击
that ended Enzo Womack's career five years ago.
我看恩佐被杀的原因已经明朗了
I think we just figured out what got Enzo killed.
这下可不轻啊
Oh! That was a nasty hit.
什么  你们看到什么了
What? What did -- what did you see?
我想知道恩佐为什么被杀
I'd like to know what got Enzo killed.
两个BCU的右后卫  相隔五年
Both BCU right guards, who played five years apart,
在同样的赛事做出同样的假摔
faked the same trip on the same play.
为了让他们的反击失败
To make sure their running back got tackled
无法得分
and didn't score.
这简直就像我的微积分考试一样
This is like the day I took that A.P. Calculus exam.
就是打死我  我也做不出
You know, I couldn't have solved that inverse derivative problem
那道反导数的题
if my life depended on it.
别激动  别激动
Calm down. Calm down, okay?
终于轮到我给你上一课了
For once, I get to explain something to you.
弗罗斯特  你能把画面定格到两次假摔上吗
Frost, can you freeze both bad plays?
那个右后卫  还有至少另外一名球员
That right guard and at least one other player --
可能是四分卫  搞砸了2007年的比赛
probably the quarterback -- fixed that game in 2007.
五年之后的这名右后卫
Okay, and that right guard
又做出了同样的动作
fixed the same play five years later.
你是说BCU的球员
Are you saying BCU players
在两个赛季分别放弃了比赛
from two separate seasons threw games?
是操控比赛
Altered games.
如果直接放弃  就太明显了
It's too easy to get caught if you throw them.
如果仅仅是减少得分
If you just shave points...
弗罗斯特  看看两名四分卫
Frost, can we see both quarterbacks?
没错  你们看
Yeah, right there.
BCU 14  西风大学 10
两名四分卫做了同样的手势
Both quarterbacks made identical signals.
看着像  我们要放弃比赛
That says to me, "We're throwing the play."
看他们的眼睛  就在他们拍头盔之前
Watch their eyes right before they tap their helmets.
对  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
应该有个发令人  他们在看谁
We have a shot caller -- who are they looking at?
弗罗斯特  还有没有其他角度
Frost, do you have any other angles?
恩佐一定是发现了
So, Enzo must have realized
那次结束了他职业生涯的撞击并非偶然
the trip that ended his career wasn't accidental.
但右后卫为什么要假摔呢
But why would the right guard fake a trip?
恩佐是他的队友啊
Enzo was his teammate.
那些踢假球的球员不是想害他
The players who were cheating weren't trying to hurt him.
他们只是不想让他得分
They were just trying to keep him from scoring.
这样就能改变"高低"了
To change the over/under.
-一切都是为了这个  -当然了
- That's what this is about. - Of course.
什么  比什么高低
What? Over/under what?
"高低"是一种赌博
Over/under is a type of bet.
庄家在赛前宣布一个数字
Oddsmakers announce a number before a game.
这个数是他们对双方最终得分之和的猜测
It's their best guess of what the final combined score will be.
我可以赌比这个数高还是低
And I can bet over or under that number.
-没错  -好的  我想我懂了
- Yes. - Okay, I think I understand.
如果两对比分相加
So if the teams' scores, when added together,
比预计的数字低  我就赢了
are lower than predicted, I win.
对
Yes.
如果你知道有不法球员
And if you know that there are dirty players
暗中操控比赛  限制得分
that are fixing the game to keep the score down,
然后再去赌低  你就赢大了
you bet on the under, and then you win big.
没错  但大学球员为什么要作弊呢
Yeah, but why would a college player cheat,
尤其还是这样一所很有名望的大学
especially at a prestigious academic university?
BCU是丙级橄榄球队
Well, BCU is a division III football program.
既没有赞助  也没有奖学金
There's no money, no scholarships.
他们买装备的钱都是靠洗车筹款会弄来的
They're having a car-wash fundraiser to buy equipment.
找到另一个角度了  边线镜头
Got another angle -- sideline camera.
菲利普斯教练是发令人
Coach Phillips is the shot caller.
不对  再放一遍
I don't think so. Play it again.
对  对  对
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好  同时放2007年和周六的比赛
Okay, play both the 2007 game and Saturday's game.
看麦肯齐
Watch MacKenzie.
看到了吗  两次他都扔毛巾了
You see that? He dropped the towel both times.
恩佐伤口上物质的化验结果出来了
Uh, the results are back on the substance found in Enzo's wounds.
是止痛发热橡胶贴
It's analgesic heat rub.
我发现的纤维来自棉质运动胶带
And the fibers I found were from cotton sports tape.
莫拉
Maura...
你说过凶器应该有个手柄
You said the murder weapon had a hilt?
会不会是一把多功能工具  像这样的
Could it be a multipurpose tool, like this one?
有可能
Yes.
是恩佐的电话吗
Is that Enzo's phone?
你不能抢走修好电话的功劳
Okay, you don't get credit for fixing it.
-给我  -不给
- Give it to me. - No.
我也会看短信
I can look at cellphones, too.
给我  我把它接到大屏幕上
Give it to me and let me plug it in.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是他最后一条短信
Here's his last text message.
发给丹・麦肯齐的  早上7点54分
To Dan MacKenzie, 7:54 A.M.
就在他去洗车之前
Right before he went to the car wash.
我想谈谈  希望是我疯了
"Need to talk. I hope I'm crazy.
我觉得教练让BCU球员故意让球
I think coach has BCU players shaving points."
他以为他的教练作弊
He thought his coach was dirty.
希望是我疯了
"I hope I'm crazy."
不想指控他深爱的球队
We didn't want to accuse the program he loved
除非他确信不疑
unless he was sure he was right.
所以他就去找他最信任的人
So he went to the person he trusted the most --
他的前队友丹・麦肯齐
his former teammate Dan MacKenzie.
不该肿成这样啊
It shouldn't be so swollen.
我说了多少遍  让你做冷敷了
How many times I got to tell you to ice this sucker, huh?
你不能进来  女士止步的
Hey, you can't be in here. There's no women allowed.
BCU刚刚特许我了
BCU just made an exception.
有什么事吗
Well, what's this about?
我们查了你的比赛数据  丹
We checked your stats, Dan.
你以前是个不错的得分手
You were a good field-goal kicker.
但忽然有一天  你就开始射不中了
But suddenly, you started missing.
-是从那时候开始的吧  -开始什么呀
- Was that when it started? - When what started?
你故意射偏  好控制得分
You were missing kicks to shave points.
我听不懂你们在说什么
I don't know what you guys are talking about.
我们在说人的贪欲
We're talking about basic greed.
作为一名年入4万的丙级教练
Living pretty large for a guy making $40,000
你过得还真阔绰啊
as a D-III athletic trainer.
我想请律师
I want a lawyer.
你在大学期间想到了这个阴谋
You came up with this scheme in college,
但你知道恩佐不会踢假球  因为他是个好人
but you knew Enzo wouldn't cheat 'cause he was a good guy.
而且他要被选入俱乐部  你却没有
And he was going to the pros. You weren't.
他  他指控球队踢假球
He -- he -- he was accusing the team of cheating.
他会抹黑BCU的声誉
He was gonna give the BCU program a bad name.
恩佐被你杀害之前  曾给你发过短信
Enzo sent you a text before you killed him.
他以为是菲利普斯教练把球员们拉下水的
He thought coach Phillips was corrupting the players.
他怎么也想不到  其实是他的好兄弟
It never occurred to him it was his friend.
你因为涉嫌谋杀恩佐・沃马克被捕了
You're under arrest for the murder of Enzo Womack.
嘿
Hey.
你来这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
我知道你希望我装作一切都会好的
I know you wanted me to pretend that everything will be fine.
那是什么
What's that?
我做了点研究
Some research I did on
关于腰椎减压手术的
decompressive lumbar spine surgery.
我不想听
I don't wanna know.
简  你需要听听
Jane, you need to know.
为什么  他都说要离开了  莫拉
Why? I mean, he said goodbye, Maura, so...
简  如果你在乎他
Jane, if you care about him,
你会看的
you'll look.
有多糟糕
How bad is it?
很糟
Bad.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我知道就好了
I wish I knew.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：zeez 浮世闲生 喜乐儿 janice 陈小圈 十九罗汉
校对：zeez   时间轴：JimmyBeck 密斯恩
后期：随风飞翔      总监   zeez
妙女神探  第三季第十四集
&神探
妙女&
第十四集
第三季
■